Guide to the University of Pittsburgh Archives Photographs, 1810-2006 UA.Photos
ULS Archives & Special Collections
University of Pittsburgh Archives Photograph Collection
ca. 1810-2006
ULS Archives & Special Collections
University of Pittsburgh
UA.Photos
5 Linear Feet (4 boxes)
These are photographs from various sources documenting University people, events and places taken by University of Pittsburgh photographers.
Access Restrictions
No restrictions.
Acquisition Information
These photographs have been deposited by several University offices including the University Times, Student Affairs, Public Affairs and CIDDE.
Previous Citation
University of Pittsburgh Archives Photograph Collection, 1810-2006, UA.Photos, University Archives, Archives Service Center, University of Pittsburgh
Scope and Content Notes
This is a collection of photographs gathered from several University offices and sources between 2007-2011. The photographs are of various, buildings, events, and people affiliated with the University taken between 1880-2006. Painted portraits of University officials bear their original creation date though were photographed in the twentieth century.
Accruals
Additional photographs are expected to be added to the collection on an ongoing basis as they are deposited.
Related Material
University Archives Information Files, University Archives, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
Arrangement
There is no specific arrangement to the photographs.
Negatives (Photographic); Photographs; Universities and colleges -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh -- Photographs; University of Pittsburgh; University of Pittsburgh
- Staff Association Council and SAB (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Authors (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Medical Material/Nursing Center (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Maintenance/Engineers/Computers/Etc. (Box 1, Folder 4)
- United Way Photo/AGF (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Supercomputer (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Unlabeled Contacts and Negatives (Box 1, Folder 7)
  Scope and Content Notes
  Chancellor's residence, Syria Mosque demolition, ShadyOak
- Unlabeled, Line Drawing of Lodge (Box 1, Folder 8)
- New Faculty 1992/1993 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Apple for the Teacher Awards, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- LG II Group, March 3, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Bio Tech Center and Opening, August 31, 1992 and April 2, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  J. Dennis O'Connor, Gov. Robert Casey, Tom Forester,
- Indian Ambassador, August 20, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Chancellor's Picnics, September 1, 1992 and August 31, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  Mary Brisco, Ben Tuchi, J. Dennis O'Connor, Dean Epperson, Cathedral Lawn with students
- Day of Caring, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- New University Police Officers, September 8, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- United Way Kickoff Breakfast, October 13, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Blood Drive, October 26, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Staff Association Council Officers and Meetings, June 22, 1992 and November 5, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Pitt Administrators and Professors, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  Ben Tuchi, Conrad Neuner, Edward Permar, Bruce Dobler, Edward Striker, Dennis Looney, Charles Watson
- Faculty Meetings and Faculty Senate Meetings, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  Nathan Hershey, James Holland, Richard Tobias, Herb Chesler, Toby Chapman, Phil Wion, Eva Broscius, Dennis Brutus, Art Ramicone, Karen Rondestvedt, Donald Henderson
- "Jump Start" Press Conference, October 9, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Software Pirates, November 11, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- European Community Consuls General, November 10, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  Alberta Sbragia
- Grant Presentation, December 11, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  O'Connor, John Wilds
- Staff Recognition Reception, December 15, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Masonic Temple, Alumni Hall, November 11, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Lantern Night Display, August 8, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Sutherland Hall, August 30, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- First Church of Christ the Scientist, location unknown, July 16, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Executive Committee, Board of Trustees, July 16, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Board of Trustees, June 19, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  John Marous' last meeting as Chairman.
- NCAA Investigation Press Conference, May 11, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Herb Needleman Hearings, April 13, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Graduation, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- James Kehl (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Scouting for Food, June 4, 1998 and April 21, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Honors Convocation and Reception Following, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  August Wilson, Vernell Lillie, Donald Henderson
- Chancellors' Award Winners, March 11, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  Theodore Cohen and Walter Goldberg
- Graham Hatfull, April 16, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Steam Project, February 17, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Heinz Windows, January 21, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Feburary 18, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Board of Trustees, Installation and Lectures, February 25-27, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Senate Council Meetings, October 12, 1998; May 11, 1998; and November 13, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  J. Dennis O'Connor, Thomas Detre, Donald Henderson, Peter Kohler, Herb Chesler, Barbara Epstein, Nathan Hershey, James Maher, Mark Nordenberg.
- Env. Port, April 30, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Interactive Video, January 15, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Freddie Fu, February 4, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- University Art Gallery Faculty Show, January 30, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- November 7, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Phone Book Recycling, November 15, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Board of Trustees, November 22, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Heinz Lecture: Nelson Mandela, December 6, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 51-52)
- Barbara Sizemore Interview, March 19, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 53)
- L. Oval Jaynes, New Athletic Director, August 13, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Materials Science Grant, School of Engineering, October 14, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  Fred Petit
- United Faculty Press Conference, unknown (Box 1, Folder 56)
- Pitt Building Construction Sites, August-September 1991 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  BioMedical Sciences Tower, Peterson
- Pitt Professors, March-April, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  Chenits Pettigrew, UCEP; J. O'Brien Schaefer, English; Kanchan Rao, Medicine; William Brown, Law; Joel Peterson, Mech E.; Kumbakonam R. Rajgopal; Carl R. Fuhrman, Medicine; Werner Rheinboldt, Mathematics; Seymore Drescher, History.
- H. John Heinz, III Funeral at Heinz Chapel, April 8, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 59)
- Honors Convocation, March 13, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  Louis W. Sullivan, HHS
- Smoking, January 30, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 61)
- Dormitory Site and Pitt Stadium, February 19, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 62)
- Faculty Unionization Meeting, February 13, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 63)
- Jiri Nehnevajsa, Sociology, March 1, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 64)
- Meeting, Posvar and others, March 7, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 65)
- Iraq War Protest, January 14, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 66)
- Meeting, Posvar, January 10, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 67)
- Board of Trustees Meeting, February 19, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  Mark Nordenberg, Ana Guzman?, Al Novak, Alumni Association Scholarship Fund.
- Faculty Assembly Meeting, February 3, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  Costantino, Chesler, Davis, Van Beck Hall, Holland, Ginsberg, Rougeux, Macleod
- Copy Cat Grand Opening, May 8, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 70)
- Reception for Peter Koehler, May 6, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  Mark Nordenberg, Burkhart Holzner,
- Tour of Cathedral, participants unknown, June 2, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 72)
- June 18, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 73)
- Adopt-A-Block Pitt Volunteers on Bouquet St., June 24, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 74)
- William Pitt Union Event, June 24, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 75)
- UP Bradford, Paddling to Pittsburgh, August 12, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 76)
- School of Medicine White Coat Ceremony, August 9, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 77)
- August 11, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 78)
- Day of Caring, September 9, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 79)
- Douglas Branson, September 11, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 80)
- Researchers, September 18, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 81)
- Pennsylvania Hall Demolition, October 29, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 82)
- Staff Association Council Meeting, November 4, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 83)
- November 19, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 84)
- Staff Recognition, December 9, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 85)
- Computer Learning Center, December 2, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 86)
- Bouquet Gardens Ground Breaking, December 1, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 87)
- Sophomore Reception, December 2, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 88)
- Institutional Research, December 4, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 89)
- Lothrop Fitness Center, January 5, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 90)
- Blizzard Photos, January 10, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 91)
- AGIA Art People, February 8, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 92)
- CIDDE Check Presentation, February 21, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 93)
- Board Meeting, February 22, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 94)
- Honors Convocation, February 28, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 95)
- Founders Day, February 29, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 96)
- Tree Removal, March 4, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 97)
- Faculty Show at Frick Fine Arts, March 15, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 98)
- April 18, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 99)
- Where White Men Fear to Tread Book Signing (Box 1, Folder 100)
- SAJNA(?) (Box 1, Folder 101)
- Commencement, April 28, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 102)
- German Ambassador, September 16, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 103)
- Kathleen Blue, September 19, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 104)
- Law Lecture, September 29, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 105)
- Blood Drive, October 16, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 106)
- Starzl Institute (Box 1, Folder 107)
- Help Tables, December 4, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 108)
- Staff Recognition, December 11, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 109)
- Cabinet Makers and Refinishers (Box 1, Folder 110)
- SAC Meeting, May 4, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 111)
- Diversity Seminar, May 5, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 112)
- Senate Council Meeting, May 17, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 113)
- Board of Trustees/F.Rubenstein Last Day as Chair/M.Nordenberg Introduced as Interim Chancellor, June 22, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 114)
- New Football Facilities, August 8, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 115)
- Convocation 95, August 26, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 116)
- "Night of the Panther", August 29, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 117)
- Agreement Signing, September 14, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 118)
- Staff Association Council Offices, September 20, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 119)
- Volunteer Fair, September 18, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 120)
- Eric Beckman, September ??, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 121)
- Students Cleaning, October 7, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 122)
- Mini Police Station, October 6, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 123)
- Chancellor's Conference, October 10, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 124)
- District Ed. Room, October 13, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 125)
- Union Debate, October 18, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 126)
- Board of Trustees, October 19, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 127)
- Gamelan, November 30, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 128)
- Staff Recognition, December 13, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 129)
- Board of Trustees Meeting, February 16, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 130)
- University Senate Council Meeting: O'Connor Resignation Announcement, March 10, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 131)
- Chocolate Festival, March 31, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 132)
- Faculty Assembly Meeting, October 1, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 133)
- Teacher Awards, October 12, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 134)
- Lazer Tag, October 13, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 135)
- Fireworks/Keg Roll, March 14-15, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 136)
- Laser Storm/Homecoming "WDVE", October 14, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 137)
- Employee Assistance Program/Adaptive Equipment Demo, October 19, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 138)
- Board of Trustees, October 21, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 139)
- Panel Discussion, November 18, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 140)
- Post-Doc Reception, September 7, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 141)
- 427 Memorial, September 19, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 142)
- Shane, June 9, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 143)
- Freshman Move-in, August 26, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 144)
- Freshman Convocation, August 27, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 145)
- Retirement, August 25, 1994 and August 29, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 146)
- Faculty Senate Meeting, June 7, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 147)
- Dr. Bernard Fisher, July 19, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 148)
- New Signage, July 14, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 149)
- Be A Sport, May 17, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 150)
- Bicycle Day, May 18, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 151)
- Commencement, May 2, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 152)
- Chancellors Awards Winners Herbert Needleman, Jim Cunningham, Wm. Thomas, April 8, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 153)
- Untitled Photos (Box 1, Folder 154)
- Frick Art Gallery, February ??, 1982 and September ??, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 155)
- UP Juried Members Exhibit, March ??, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 156)
- Sculpture by Women in 80's UPG Gallery, November ??, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 157)
- Studio Arts Faculty Exhibit, December ?? 1985-January ??, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 158)
- City Visions Exhibit, November ??, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 159)
- GSB Art, September ??, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 160)
- University Times Calendar Page-June 18 Issues (Box 1, Folder 161)
- Gimbel Collection Exhibit, January ??, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 162)
- African Art, March ??, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 163)
- UP Gallery Faculty Exhibit, January ??, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 164)
- Therapeutic Learning Center Calendar (Box 1, Folder 165)
- Untitled Photos (Box 1, Folder 166)
- 1st Day, August 1, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 166-A)
- University Times: Dr. Ruben Tenicela's Skeleton Coatrack "Pain and Suffering", 1972 (Box 1, Folder 167)
- Board of Trustees, June 13, 1991 and July 19, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 168)
- Board Meeting and Tour (Box 1, Folder 169)
- Syria Mosque/Mosque Demolition, June 11, 1990 and August 27, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 170)
- Press Conference, June 10, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 171)
- Senate Council Meetings, June 9, 1997/April 10, 2000/March 22, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 172)
- Marathon, May 5, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 173)
- New Dormitories, March 25, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 174)
- Joel Abrams, March 25, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 175)
- Robert Pearloff, May 16, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 176)
- O'Connor Election, May 1, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 177)
- Commencement, April 28, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 178)
- Scouting For Food, April 28, 1991 and April 30, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 179)
- Posvar Reception (Box 1, Folder 180)
- Library and Information Sciences Speaker A. Okerson (Box 1, Folder 181)
- January 18, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 182)
- David Miller, January 20, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 183)
- Professor David Brumble, January 24, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 184)
- Herberman & Griffin, February 18, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 185)
- Susan Albrecht, February 22, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 186)
- Faculty Assembly, November 30, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 187)
- Dean's Forum on International Ethics, unknown (Box 1, Folder 188)
- New Police Chief, December 23, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 189)
- Staff Recognition, December 10, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 190)
- Protest, April 4, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 191)
- Demolition Forbes and Bouquet, April 19, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 192)
- Hall, May 10, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 193)
- Korean War Flag Raising Ceremony, May 19, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 194)
- May 22, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 195)
- Ridgeway Center, May 30, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 196)
- Jeffrey Lawrence, June 2, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 197)
- Holzer Retirement, June 7, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 198)
- Dennis McManus, July 14, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 199)
- Korean War Conference, June 14, 2000 and June 15, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 200)
- 8/24/2000, August 24, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 201)
- John Baker, March 28, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 202)
- Freshman Convocation 8/25/05, August 25, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 203)
- New Football Coach, December 16, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 204)
- Board of Trustees, February 20, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 205)
- Founders Day, February 27, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 206)
- Honors Convocation, February 28, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 207)
- Salman Rushdie, April 9, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 208)
- Heinz Tree Dedication, May 17, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 209)
- Speakers/Visitors #1 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Speakers/Visitors #2 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Speakers/Visitors #3 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Speakers/Visitors #4 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Speakers/Visitors #5 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Chautauqua At Pitt #1 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Chautauqua At Pitt #2 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Chautauqua At Pitt #3 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Pitt-Greensburg (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Pitt-Titusville (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Samuel Yellin Metalworkers (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Bicentennial #1 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Bicentennial #2 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Bicentennial #3 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Pitt-Bradford (Box 2, Folder 15)
- O'Conner Photos #1 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- O'Conner Photos #2 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- O'Conner Photos #3 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Posvar Photos #1 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Posvar Photos #2 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Construction Photos #1 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Construction Photos #2 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Bicentennial Commencement/Honors Convocation Photos #1, 1975 and 1981 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Bicentennial Commencement/Honors Convocation Photos #2, 1980s (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Bicentennial Commencement/Honors Convocation Photos #3, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Bicentennial Commencement/Honors Convocation Photos #4, 1983 and 1986 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- University Times Pitt Professor Photos #1 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- U-Times Pitt Professor Photos #2 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- U-Times Pitt Professor Photos #3 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- U-Times Pitt Professor Photos #4 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- U-Times Pitt Professor Photos #5 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- U-Times Pitt Professor Photos #6 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- U-Times Pitt Professor Photos #7 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- U-Times Pitt Professor Photos #8 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- U-Times Pitt Professor Photos #9 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- U-Times Pitt Professor Photos #10 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- U-Times Pitt Professor Photos #11 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- U-Times Pitt Professor Photos #12 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- U-Times Pitt Professor Photos #13 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- U-Times Miscellaneous Photos #1 (Box 2, Folder 40)
- U-Times Miscellaneous Photos #2 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- U-Times Miscellaneous Photos #3 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- U-Times Miscellaneous Photos #4 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- U-Times Miscellaneous Photos #5 (Box 2, Folder 44)
- U-Times Miscellaneous Photos #6 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- U-Times Miscellaneous Photos #7 (Box 2, Folder 46)
- U-Times Miscellaneous Photos #8 (Box 2, Folder 47)
- U-Times Miscellaneous Photos #9 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- U-Times Miscellaneous Photos #10 (Box 2, Folder 49)
- U-Times Miscellaneous Photos #11 (Box 2, Folder 50)
- U-Times Miscellaneous Photos #12 (Box 2, Folder 51)
- U-Times Miscellaneous Photos #13 (Box 2, Folder 52)
- U-Times Miscellaneous Photos #14 (Box 2, Folder 53)
- U-Times Miscellaneous Photos #15 (Box 2, Folder 54)
- U-Times Miscellaneous Photos #16 (Box 2, Folder 55)
- U-Times Miscellaneous Photos #17 (Box 2, Folder 56)
- U-Times Miscellaneous Photos #18 (Box 2, Folder 57)
- U-Times Miscellaneous Photos #19 (Box 2, Folder 58)
- U-Times Miscellaneous Photos #20 (Box 2, Folder 59)
- U-Times Miscellaneous Photos #21 (Box 2, Folder 60)
- U-Times Miscellaneous Photos #22 (Box 2, Folder 61)
- U-Times Miscellaneous Photos #23 (Box 2, Folder 62)
- U-Times Miscellaneous Photos #24 (Box 2, Folder 63)
- U-Times Miscellaneous Photos #25 (Box 2, Folder 64)
- U-Times Miscellaneous Photos #26 (Box 2, Folder 65)
- U-Times Miscellaneous Photos #27 (Box 2, Folder 66)
- U-Times Miscellaneous Photos #28 (Box 2, Folder 67)
- Unlabeled Negatives #1 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Unlabeled Contacts #1 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Unlabeled Contacts #2 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Front of Cathedral, Work Prints (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Univeristy Community Educational Program (UCEP) Slides #1 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- UCEP Slides #2 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Cathedral Slides, unknown (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Holiday Party/Celebration-UCEP, 1997? (Box 3, Folder 8)
- UCEP-unknown event-WPU Kurtzman Room, Between 1992 and 1998 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- UCEP Staff 2002 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- UCEP: End of Summer Program Celebration/Recognition, August ??, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- 1930s-era Reunion CAS, October 13, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- College of Arts and Sciences 1942 Reunion, unknown (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Europe and Soviet Union, unknown (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Professor Jeremy Sabloff, February 22, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Gail McGuire, Telemarketing Staff, July 3, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Claudene George, unknown (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Stanford Lyons, unknown (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Harold Brown, unknown (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Nicole Deman, unknown (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Darlington Library, November 5, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Women's Air Corps Reunion, June ??, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Reunion College of Arts and Sciences 1940, April 26, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Calculus Lab, February 19, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- "Student Studying", November 4, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Dean Mary Lou Soffa, June 4, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Dean Mary Briscoe, June 3, 1992 and June 4, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Fundraisers, May ??, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- D. Baranevevo, February 24, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- George Bandik, February 22, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- D. Evans/Skazac/D. Greenwich, unknown (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Professor Lauren Resnick, February 23, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Beverly Michael, March 2, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Graham Hatfull, March 2, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Michael Boykin, March 6, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Peter Koehler, July 2, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Pitt Stadium, unknown (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Kristin Zagst, March 4, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Advisor and Student, July 30, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Fred Koloc, August 30, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Werner Tresken, July 26, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 40)
- Susan Andrade, July 28, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 41)
- CAS Sampler: Media and the Message, March 20, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 42)
- Renee McDonald, October 27, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 43)
- Fall Mailer, October 18, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 44)
- Deans (Box 3, Folder 45)
- Chemistry Deptartment, Vans? (Box 3, Folder 46)
- English Deptartment Reception, April 19, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 47)
- Womes Air Corps Reunion, Negatives, June 3, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 48)
- Faculty of Arts and Sciences, Board of Visitors, October 28, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 49)
- Computer Music, February 19, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 50)
- Mary Edmunds, October 21, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 51)
- Commencement and Reunion JBD, April 26, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 52)
- Arts and Sciences Saturday Sampler, March 21, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 53)
- #2 Sampler Creative Mind at Work, unknown (Box 3, Folder 54)
- CAS Event, Journey to Neptune, Negatives, November 11 (Box 3, Folder 54-A)
- AGF Board Reception Dinner, May 12, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 55)
- Spotlight on Science, November 2, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 55-A)
- Arts and Sciences Saturday Sampler, March 21, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 56)
- Allison McQueen, unknown (Box 3, Folder 57)
- Hewitt, unknown (Box 3, Folder 58)
- Gail Golden, unknown (Box 3, Folder 59)
- Nathan Urban, July 23, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 60)
- Peter Irvine, July 26, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 61)
- Derrick and Anna Schreihofer, unknown (Box 3, Folder 62)
- Parents Day, October 2, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 63)
- CAS Reception, October 4, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 64)
- 1980 Mouth Protection Program (Box 3, Folder 65)
- Dental Annex Reconstruction, 1987-1990 (Box 3, Folder 66)
- Mount Summit Inn 25th Anniversary Awards, June 1987 (Box 3, Folder 67)
- Mouthguard Day 1985 (Box 3, Folder 68)
- Dental School-ASDA Day 1981 (Box 3, Folder 69)
- Dental School Photos #1 (Box 3, Folder 70)
- Dental School Photos #2 (Box 3, Folder 71)
- Dental School Photos #3 (Box 3, Folder 72)
- Dental School Photos #4 (Box 3, Folder 73)
- Dental School Photos #5 (Box 3, Folder 74)
- Dental School Photos #6 (Box 3, Folder 75)
- Dental School Photos #7 (Box 3, Folder 76)
- Dental School Photos #8 (Box 3, Folder 77)
- Dental School Photos #9 (Box 3, Folder 78)
- Dental School Photos #10 (Box 3, Folder 79)
- Dental School Photos #11 (Box 3, Folder 80)
- Dental School Photos #12 (Box 3, Folder 81)
- Pitt in London, unknown (Box 3, Folder 82)
- Koehler and Briscoe #1 (Box 3, Folder 83)
- Koehler and Briscoe #2 (Box 3, Folder 84)
- Holiday Party-1st Floor Cathedral #1, unknown (Box 3, Folder 85)
- Holiday Party-1st Floor Cathedral #2, unknown (Box 3, Folder 86)